MUHAMMAD TAHIR

MECHANICAL FOREMAN



+92301-7076112



kashifamjad402@gmail.com



33100-0695995-9



P-1151, Mohallah Abbas Park, Street 01, Faisalabad, Pakistan

About Me

I am a skilled mechanical professional with 15 years of work experience as mechanical Foreman, Supervisor, head technician and fitter. I have worked in well reputed textile mills of Faisalabad and now seeking to increase my skills and experience in your esteemed organization.

Experience

Kamal Textile Mills, Oct 2022 - Continue

Mechanical Foreman

Working on maintenance and all other mechanical related tasks on Dyeing, Printing, finishing and bleaching machines.

Interloop, June 2022 - Oct 2022

Senior Technician

Worked on finishing machines and hosiery.

Sitara Textile Mills, Jan 2013 - June 2022

Mechanical Supervisor

Working on maintenance and all other mechanical related tasks on Dyeing, Printing, finishing and bleaching machines.

Masood Textile Mills, June 2010 - Nov 2013

Head Fitter

Working on maintenance and all other mechanical related tasks on Dyeing, Printing, finishing and bleaching machines.

Ashraf Lubricant, April 2010 - June 2005

Fabricator

Worked related to Fabrication and welding.

Sitara Engineering Works, Aug 2001 - June 2005

Fitter

Worked in mechanical workshop.

Education

Intermediate, 2012

Allama Iqbal Open university

Matric, 2009

Allama Iqbal Open university

Diploma of Office Management, 2012

Punjab Computer College, Faisalabad